<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arduino Singer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="acb_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="lbl_name">Name</string>
    <string name="lbl_location">Location</string>
    <string name="lbl_desc">Description</string>
    <string name="contDesc_pictureplace">Place picture</string>
    <string name="acb_save">Save</string>
    <string name="acb_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="acb_search">Search a place</string>
    <string name="acb_associate_contact">Associate contact</string>
    <string name="acb_remove_search_results">Remove search results</string>
    <string name="acb_sort_by">Sort by...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_place_details">PlaceDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="txt_associated_contacts">Associated contacts:</string>
    <string name="CAB_delete_place">Delete place</string>
    <string name="CAB_share_place">Share this place!</string>
    <string name="toast_connected_successfully">Connected to you Bluetooth device successfully!</string>
    <string name="toast_not_connected_yet">There is no connection to Bluetooth device yet! Wait a couple of seconds&#8230;</string>
    <string name="desc_20century">
        Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation  is an American film studio currently owned by 21st Century Fox.\n\n
        20th Century Fox is known for its now-iconic searchlight structure logo. Its fanfare was originally composed
        in 1933 by Alfred Newman, who became the head of Twentieth Century-Fox\'s music department from 1940 until the
        1960s. It was re-recorded in 1935 when 20th Century-Fox was officially established.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_blue">
        "Blue (Da Ba Dee)" is a hit song by the Italian music group Eiffel 65. It was released on 15 January 1999 as
        the lead single from their debut album Europop. The song is the group\'s most popular single, reaching number
        one in many countries such as Ireland, the United Kingdom etc.\n
        The song also received a Grammy Award nomination for Best Dance Recording at the 2001 Grammy Awards.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_equipoa">
        The A-Team is an American action-adventure television series that ran on NBC from 1983 to 1987 about members
        of a fictitious former United States Army Special Forces unit. The series was created by Stephen J. Cannell
        and Frank Lupo. A feature film based on the series was released by 20th Century Fox in June 2010.\n\n
        The original main theme by Mike Post and Pete Carpenter was released on the vinyl LP Mike Post – Television
        Theme Songs and again on the Mike Post – Mike Post LP. Though no original music other than the theme has been
        released, in 1984 Silva Screen issued an album of re-recorded material from the series conducted by Daniel Caine.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_indianajones">
        Henry Walton "Indiana" Jones Jr. is a fictional character and the protagonist of the Indiana Jones franchise.
        Jones is most famously played by Harrison Ford and has also been portrayed by River Phoenix.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_thesimpsons">
        The Simpsons is an American animated sitcom created by Matt Groening for the Fox Broadcasting Company. The series
        is a satirical depiction of working-class life epitomized by the Simpson family, which consists of Homer, Marge,
        Bart, Lisa, and Maggie. Since its debut on December 17, 1989, 618 episodes of The Simpsons have been broadcast.
        It is the longest-running American sitcom and the longest-running American animated program, and, in 2009, it
        surpassed Gunsmoke as the longest-running American scripted primetime television series.\n\n
        The series\' distinctive theme song was composed by musician Danny Elfman in 1989, after Groening approached him
        requesting a retro style piece. This piece has been noted by Elfman as the most popular of his career.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_maribros">
        Mario Bros  is a platform game published and developed for arcades by Nintendo in 1983. It was created by Shigeru
        Miyamoto. It has been featured as a minigame in the Super Mario Advance series and numerous other games. In the
        game, Mario is portrayed as an Italian-American plumber who, along with his younger brother Luigi, has to defeat
        creatures that have been coming from the sewers below New York City. This song has been used in later video games,
        including Dance Dance Revolution Mario Mix[10] and Super Smash Bros. Brawl.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_popeye">
        Popeye the Sailor is a cartoon fictional character created by Elzie Crisler Segar. Popeye’s theme song, titled
        "I\'m Popeye The Sailor Man", composed by Sammy Lerner in 1933 for Fleischer’s first Popeye the Sailor cartoon,
        has become forever associated with the sailor. The Sailor\'s Hornpipe has often been used as an introduction to
        Popeye\'s theme song.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_starwars">
        Star Wars is an American epic space opera franchise, centered on a film series created by George Lucas. It depicts
        the adventures of various characters "a long time ago in a galaxy far, far away". After its debut, Rogue One
        received generally positive reviews, with its performances, action sequences, soundtrack, visual effects and darker
        tone being praised. The film grossed over $500 million worldwide within a week of its release.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_takeonme">
        "Take On Me" is a song by Norwegian synthpop band A-ha. Written by the band members, the original version was produced
        by Tony Mansfield and remixed by John Ratcliff. The second version of the song was produced by Alan Tarney for the
        group\'s debut studio album Hunting High and Low (1985). The song combines synthpop with a varied instrumentation that
        includes acoustic guitars, keyboards and drums.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_zelda">
        The Legend of Zelda[a] is a high-fantasy action-adventure video game series created by Japanese game designers Shigeru
        Miyamoto and Takashi Tezuka. It is primarily developed and published by Nintendo, although some portable installments
        have been outsourced to Capcom, Vanpool and Grezzo. Ocarina of Time is "[one of the] first contemporary non-dance
        title[s] to feature music-making as part of its gameplay", using music as a heuristic device and requiring the player
        to utilise songs to progress in the game – a game mechanic that is also present in Majora\'s Mask.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_missionimpossible">
        Mission: Impossible is a series of action spy thriller films based on the television series of the same name, produced
        by and starring Tom Cruise as Impossible Missions Force (IMF) agent Ethan Hunt. Beginning in 1996, the films follow the
        missions of the IMF\'s main field team under the leadership of Hunt, who is forced to take over after the team is betrayed
        from within in the first film. The series is the 18th-highest-grossing film series of all time, with a worldwide gross of
        over $2 billion to date. U2 band members Larry Mullen, Jr. and Adam Clayton produced an electronic dance version of the
        original theme song. The song went into top ten of music charts around the world, and was nominated for the Grammy Award
        for Best Pop Instrumental Performance. The film was the third-highest-grossing of the year and received positive reviews
        from film critics.
    </string>
    <string name="lyric_twentycentury">20thCenFox:d=16,o=5,b=140:b,8p,b,b,2b,p,c6,32p,b,32p,c6,32p,b,32p,c6,32p,b,8p,b,b,b,32p,b,32p,b,32p,b,32p,b,32p,b,32p,b,32p,g#,32p,a,32p,b,8p,b,b,2b,4p,8e,8g#,8b,1c#6,8f#,8a,8c#6,1e6,8a,8c#6,8e6,1e6,8b,8g#,8a,2b</string>
    <string name="lyric_blue">Blue:d=4,o=5,b=125:8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8c6,8f,8a,8a#,8p,8g,8a#,8d6,8d#6,8g,8d6,8c6,8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8c6,8f,8a,8a#,8p,8g,8a#,8d6,8d#6,8g,8d6,8c6,8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8c6,8f,8a,8a#,a#,a#,a#.,2p,a,a#,8g,8a#,8c6,8c6,8a,a#,8f,8a#,8d6,d#6,8d6,8c6,a#,8f,8a#,8c6,8c6,8a,a#,8f,a#,8d6,8d#6,8g,8d6,8c6,8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8c6,8f,8a,4a#,8g,8a#,8d6,8d#6,8g,8d6,8c6,8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8c6,8f,8a,4a#,8g,8a#,8d6,8d#6,8g,8d6,8c6,8a#,8d,8g,8a#,8a,8c,8f,2g</string>
    <string name="lyric_equipoa">A-Team:d=8,o=5,b=125:4d#6,a#,2d#6,16p,g#,4a#,4d#.,p,16g,16a#,d#6,a#,f6,2d#6,16p,c#.6,16c6,16a#,g#.,2a#</string>
    <string name="lyric_indianajones">Indiana:d=4,o=5,b=250:e,8p,8f,8g,8p,1c6,8p.,d,8p,8e,1f,p.,g,8p,8a,8b,8p,1f6,p,a,8p,8b,2c6,2d6,2e6,e,8p,8f,8g,8p,1c6,p,d6,8p,8e6,1f.6,g,8p,8g,e.6,8p,d6,8p,8g,e.6,8p,d6,8p,8g,f.6,8p,e6,8p,8d6,2c6</string>
    <string name="lyric_lossimpsons">The Simpsons:d=4,o=5,b=160:c.6,e6,f#6,8a6,g.6,e6,c6,8a,8f#,8f#,8f#,2g,8p,8p,8f#,8f#,8f#,8g,a#.,8c6,8c6,8c6,c6</string>
    <string name="lyric_mariobros">smb:d=4,o=5,b=100:16e6,16e6,32p,8e6,16c6,8e6,8g6,8p,8g,8p,8c6,16p,8g,16p,8e,16p,8a,8b,16a#,8a,16g.,16e6,16g6,8a6,16f6,8g6,8e6,16c6,16d6,8b,16p,8c6,16p,8g,16p,8e,16p,8a,8b,16a#,8a,16g.,16e6,16g6,8a6,16f6,8g6,8e6,16c6,16d6,8b,8p,16g6,16f#6,16f6,16d#6,16p,16e6,16p,16g#,16a,16c6,16p,16a,16c6,16d6,8p,16g6,16f#6,16f6,16d#6,16p,16e6,16p,16c7,16p,16c7,16c7,p,16g6,16f#6,16f6,16d#6,16p,16e6,16p,16g#,16a,16c6,16p,16a,16c6,16d6,8p,16d#6,8p,16d6,8p,16c6</string>
    <string name="lyric_popeye">Popeye:d=4,o=5,b=140:16g.,16f.,16g.,16p,32p,16c.,16p,32p,16c.,16p,32p,16e.,16d.,16c.,16d.,16e.,16f.,g,8p,16a,16f,16a,16c6,16b,16a,16g,16a,16g,8e,16g,16g,16g,16g,8a,16b,32c6,32b,32c6,32b,32c6,32b,8c6</string>
    <string name="lyric_starwars">StarWars:d=4,o=5,b=45:32p,32f#,32f#,32f#,8b.,8f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32c#6,8b.6,16f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32c#6,8b.6,16f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32e6,8c#.6,32f#,32f#,32f#,8b.,8f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32c#6,8b.6,16f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32c#6,8b.6,16f#.6,32e6,32d#6,32e6,8c#6</string>
    <string name="lyric_takeonme">TakeOnMe:d=4,o=4,b=160:8f#5,8f#5,8f#5,8d5,8p,8b,8p,8e5,8p,8e5,8p,8e5,8g#5,8g#5,8a5,8b5,8a5,8a5,8a5,8e5,8p,8d5,8p,8f#5,8p,8f#5,8p,8f#5,8e5,8e5,8f#5,8e5,8f#5,8f#5,8f#5,8d5,8p,8b,8p,8e5,8p,8e5,8p,8e5,8g#5,8g#5,8a5,8b5,8a5,8a5,8a5,8e5,8p,8d5,8p,8f#5,8p,8f#5,8p,8f#5,8e5,8e5</string>
    <string name="lyric_zelda">Zelda1:d=4,o=5,b=125:a#,f.,8a#,16a#,16c6,16d6,16d#6,2f6,8p,8f6,16f.6,16f#6,16g#.6,2a#.6,16a#.6,16g#6,16f#.6,8g#.6,16f#.6,2f6,f6,8d#6,16d#6,16f6,2f#6,8f6,8d#6,8c#6,16c#6,16d#6,2f6,8d#6,8c#6,8c6,16c6,16d6,2e6,g6,8f6,16f,16f,8f,16f,16f,8f,16f,16f,8f,8f,a#,f.,8a#,16a#,16c6,16d6,16d#6,2f6,8p,8f6,16f.6,16f#6,16g#.6,2a#.6,c#7,c7,2a6,f6,2f#.6,a#6,a6,2f6,f6,2f#.6,a#6,a6,2f6,d6,2d#.6,f#6,f6,2c#6,a#,c6,16d6,2e6,g6,8f6,16f,16f,8f,16f,16f,8f,16f,16f,8f,8f</string>
    <string name="lyric_missionimpossible">Mission Impossible:d=16,o=5,b=100:32d,32d#,32d,32d#,32d,32d#,32d,32d#,32d,32d,32d#,32e,32f,32f#,32g,g,8p,g,8p,a#,p,c6,p,g,8p,g,8p,f,p,f#,p,g,8p,g,8p,a#,p,c6,p,g,8p,g,8p,f,p,f#,p,a#,g,2d,32p,a#,g,2c#,32p,a#,g,2c,p,a#4,c</string>
    <string name="song_image_twentycentury">twentycentury</string>
    <string name="song_image_blue">blue</string>
    <string name="song_image_equipoa">equipoa</string>
    <string name="song_image_indianajones">indianajones</string>
    <string name="song_image_losimpsons">lossimpsons</string>
    <string name="song_image_mariobros">mariobross</string>
    <string name="song_image_popeye">popeye</string>
    <string name="song_image_starwars">starwars</string>
    <string name="song_image_takeonme">takeonme</string>
    <string name="song_image_zelda">zelda</string>
    <string name="song_image_missionimpossible">missionimpossible</string>

    <string name="lbl_neighborhood">Neighborhood</string>
    <string name="lbl_longitude">longitude:</string>
    <string name="lbl_latitude">latitude:</string>
    <string name="txt_hintLongitude">e.g 50.2715</string>
    <string name="txt_hintLatitude">e.g -12.9406</string>
    <string name="txt_useGPS">Use GPS</string>
    <string name="txt_NA_coordinates">(N/A , N/A)</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design are: typography, grids, space, scale and color."
    </string>
</resources>
